http://www.bingobugle.ca/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
At Bingo Bugle, accessible from http://www.bingobugle.ca, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Bingo Bugle and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at support@bingobugle.ca
Log Files
Bingo Bugle follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Like any other website, Bingo Bugle uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.
Google DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.website.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads
Our Advertising Partners
Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.
Google
https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads
Privacy Policies
You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Bingo Bugle.
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Bingo Bugle, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that Bingo Bugle has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third Pary Privacy Policies
Bingo Bugle’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?
Children’s Information
Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.
Bingo Bugle does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This Privacy Policy ) applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Bingo Bugle. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
Recent Posts
Benefits and Uses of CBD Oil
Important Things to Know about Landscaping
Advantages of Retaining Wall System Installation in Your Landscape
Considerations to Make When Hiring a Speech Therapist
WAYS IN MAKING YOUR HOME SMELLING GOOD AND FRESH
Search for:
Bingo BugleBenefits and Uses of CBD Oil  August 19, 2020While an effort to back up health keeps on growing, so too does the study on the benefits and therapeutic effects of CBD or cannabidiol. Most of such research concentrates on the manner CBD oil cooperates with the endocannabinoid system—an extensive network of CBD receptors covering several parts of the body such as the immune cells, glands, connective […] secure_adminImportant Things to Know about Landscaping  July 27, 2020In the world that we are living in, all of the people are very busy doing the things that they need to do such as work and the things that they enjoy just like going out with friends and family members. Doing anything is very difficult to insert in the schedules of people but landscaping […] secure_adminAdvantages of Retaining Wall System Installation in Your Landscape December 21, 2018If your landscape features sharp slope changes, a retaining wall system is an aspect worth integrating. Aside from giving vital structural support to huge amount of soil, a thoughtfully patterned retaining wall system can be a very attractive center of attraction for your yard. A retaining wall system also has a lot of other advantages […] secure_adminConsiderations to Make When Hiring a Speech Therapist  October 17, 2018There are many benefits a speech therapist has to offer. They are the ones we think of when we have problems in communicating verbally. However, that isn’t the only job they have in their arsenal. They help cleft palate clients, clients who have problems in swallowing, clients who needs to communicate non-verbally. Check out the […] secure_adminWAYS IN MAKING YOUR HOME SMELLING GOOD AND FRESH  October 2, 2018It is very nice to live in a place where you can inhale the fresh air and even the smell of flowers. It is quite impossible to have this experience if you are living to a place or surrounding that has a lot of trash cans and trash bins or you are very near to […] secure_admin Categories
affordable retaining walls
HOME SMELLING
Lawn Care
Speech Therapist
Uncategorized
Designed by
Elegant Themes
